Guide to the New York Produce Exchange Records 1860-1955 MS 449
New-York Historical Society
- Member meeting and committee meeting minutes. July 1914-May 1924, 1914-1924 (Offsite-box PE-58, Volume SN-139)
- Committee on Admissions minutes, Volume 12, 1916-1922 (Offsite-box PE-58, Volume SN-140)
  There are no volumes marked as volumes 1-11 for the Committee on Admissions in the collection.
- Committee on Admissions minutes, Volume 13, 1922-1925 (Offsite-box PE-59, Volume SN-141)
- Committee on Admissions minutes, Volume 14, 1925-1929 (Offsite-box PE-59, Volume SN-142)
- Committee on Admissions minutes, Volume 15, 1929-1932 (Offsite-box PE-59, Volume SN-143)
- Committee on Admissions minutes, Volume 16, 1932-1936 (Offsite-box PE-60, Volume SN-144)
- Committee on Admissions minutes, Volume 17, 1936-1938 (Offsite-box PE-60, Volume SN-145)
- Committee on Admissions minutes, Volume 18, 1938-1941 (Offsite-box PE-60, Volume SN-146)
- Committee on Admissions minutes, Volume 19, 1941-1945 (Offsite-box PE-60, Volume SN-147)
- Committee on Admissions minutes, Volume 20, 1946-1949 (Offsite-box PE-61, Volume SN-148)
- Committee on Admissions minutes, 1882-1883 (Offsite-box PE-61, Volume SN-149)
- Cotton Seed Oil (CSO). Calls/Quotations. September 1913-November 1914, 1913-1914 (Offsite-box PE-62, Volume SN-150)
  Volumes SN-150 to SN-162 are labelled as "calls" and volumes SN-163 to SN-169 and SN-182 are labelled as "quotations," but the tables in the volumes appear to have identical data.
- Cotton Seed Oil (CSO). Calls/Quotations. November 1914-February 1916, 1914-1916 (Offsite-box PE-62, Volume SN-151)
- Cotton Seed Oil (CSO). Calls/Quotations. June 1917-August 1919, 1917-1919 (Offsite-box PE-62, Volume SN-152)
- Cotton Seed Oil (CSO). Calls/Quotations. September 1919-January 1921, 1919-1921 (Offsite-box PE-63, Volume SN-153)
- Cotton Seed Oil (CSO). Calls/Quotations. January 1921-April 1922, 1921-1922 (Offsite-box PE-63, Volume SN-154)
- Cotton Seed Oil (CSO). Calls/Quotations. May 1922-August 1923, 1922-1923 (Offsite-box PE-64, Volume SN-155)
- Cotton Seed Oil (CSO). Calls/Quotations. August 1923-November 1924, 1923-1924 (Offsite-box PE-64, Volume SN-156)
- Cotton Seed Oil (CSO). Calls/Quotations. December 1924-March 1926, 1924-1926 (Offsite-box PE-65, Volume SN-157)
- Cotton Seed Oil (CSO). Calls/Quotations. July 1927-November 1928, 1927-1928 (Offsite-box PE-65, Volume SN-158)
- Cotton Seed Oil (CSO). Calls/Quotations. March 1926-July 1927, 1926-1927 (Offsite-box PE-65, Volume SN-159)
- Cotton Seed Oil (CSO). Calls/Quotations. November 1928-March 1930, 1928-1930 (Offsite-box PE-66, Volume SN-160)
- Cotton Seed Oil (CSO). Calls/Quotations. December 1930-December 1931, 1930-1931 (Offsite-box PE-66, Volume SN-161)
- Cotton Seed Oil (CSO). Calls/Quotations. December 1931-April 1933, 1931-1933 (Offsite-box PE-67, Volume SN-162)
- Cotton Seed Oil (CSO). Calls/Quotations. August 1934-September 1935, 1934-1935 (Offsite-box PE-67, Volume SN-163)
- Cotton Seed Oil (CSO). Calls/Quotations. August 1934-September 1935, 1934-1935 (Offsite-box PE-68, Volume SN-164)
- Cotton Seed Oil (CSO). Calls/Quotations. September 1935-February 1936, 1935-1936 (Offsite-box PE-68, Volume SN-165)
- Cotton Seed Oil (CSO). Calls/Quotations. October 1936-October 1937, 1936-1937 (Offsite-box PE-68, Volume SN-166)
- Cotton Seed Oil (CSO). Calls/Quotations. October 1937-November 1938, 1937-1938 (Offsite-box PE-69, Volume SN-167)
- Cotton Seed Oil (CSO). Calls/Quotations. November 1938-January 1941, 1938-1941 (Offsite-box PE-69, Volume SN-168)
- Cotton Seed Oil (CSO). Calls/Quotations. January 1941-March 1947, 1941-1947 (Offsite-box PE-70, Volume SN-169)
  See SN-182 for the next volume, ranging from 1947-1950.
- Cotton Seed Oil (CSO). Daily trades. January 1941-December 1944, 1941-1944 (Offsite-box PE-72, Volume SN-170)
  The volume cover is embossed to indicate the contents are "quotations," but the sheets themselves are labelled as "daily trades."
- Cotton Seed Oil (CSO). Daily trades. January 1945-February 1949, 1945-1949 (Offsite-box PE-73, Volume SN-171)
- Daily trades? November 1928-April 1940, 1928-1940 (Offsite-box PE-71, Volume SN-172)
  The volume is not labelled, but appears to be a record of sales of cotton seed oil (CSO), black pepper, pork, beef, and other goods. At the front of the volume is a recap of CSO sales for 1904-14 by month and an annual summary for 1904-31.
- Cotton Seed Products Committee minutes and records. November 1933-January 1943, 1933-1943 (Offsite-box PE-74, Volume SN-173)
- Cotton Seed Products Committee and Soybean Oil Committee. Joint meeting minutes. November 1946-February 1951, 1946-1951 (Offsite-box PE-74, Volume SN-174)
- Cotton Seed Products Committee minutes and records. January 1943-January 1949, 1943-1949 (Offsite-box PE-75, Volume SN-175)
- Cotton Seed Products Committee minutes and records. January 1949-March 1951, 1949-1951 (Offsite-box PE-75, Volume SN-176)
- Cotton Seed Products Committee minutes. January-September 1907 (Offsite-box PE-75, Volume SN-177)
- Cotton Seed Products Committee minutes. March 1904-January 1907, 1904-1907 (Offsite-box PE-75, Volume SN-178)
- Closing prices of prime summer yellow cotton seed oil at New York. February 1904-December 1929, 1904-1929 (Offsite-box PE-71, Volume SN-179)
  These are printed, not handwritten, sheets of data.
- Cotton Seed Products Committee minutes and records. September 1907-May 1932, 1907-1932 (Offsite-box PE-61, Volume SN-180)
- Cotton Seed Oil. Daily trades. December 1951-August 1952, 1951-1952 (Offsite-box PE-77, Volume SN-181)
- Cotton Seed Oil (CSO). Calls/Quotations. March 1947-August 1950, 1947-1950 (Offsite-box PE-76, Volume SN-182)
- Daily prices of prime summer yellow cotton seed oil (CSO) at New York. April 1909-December 1915, 1909-1915 (Offsite-box PE-76, Volume SN-183)
  Unlike volume SN-179, these are handwritten records. In addition to CSO, the records have data for pork, beef, and other goods.
- Cotton Seed Oil and Domestic Wheat. Daily trades. January 1926-January 1927, 1926-1927 (Offsite-box PE-82, Volume SN-184)
  See SN-315 to SN-319 and SN-322 to SN-330 for what appear to be earlier records of trades in these commodities.
- Cotton Seed Oil and Domestic Wheat. Daily trades. January 1927-March 1928, 1927-1928 (Offsite-box PE-83, Volume SN-185)
- Cotton Seed Oil. Daily trades. March 1928-September 1929, 1928-1929 (Offsite-box PE-84, Volume SN-186)
- Cotton Seed Oil. Daily trades. September 1929-October 1931, 1929-1931 (Offsite-box PE-85, Volume SN-187)
- Board of Trustees meeting minutes. May 1860-July 1874, 1860-1874 (Offsite-box PE-78, Volume SN-188)
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume 1. May 1861-April 1872, 1861-1872 (Offsite-box PE-61, Volume SN-189)
  Within this volume of minutes is a separate book with other summary records for the New York Commercial Association, including lists of appointments of standing and special committees, complaints, communications from similar organizations, communications from members, charter revisions, Cental system, donations, expulsions, suspensions, restorations, elections, and other data. The core of the data is from 1861-72, with some margin notations to 1880.
- Alphabetical list/register of members/subscribers, as of circa 1868 (Offsite-box PE-78, Volume SN-1900)
- Subscribers/subscription book, 1864-1869 (Offsite-box PE-78, Volume SN-191)
- Alphabetical list/register of members/subscribers, as of circa 1863 (Offsite-box PE-79, Volume SN-192)
- Subscribers/subscription book, 1869-1872 (Offsite-box PE-79, Volume SN-193)
- Alphabetical list/register of members/subscribers, as of circa 1872 (Offsite-box PE-79, Volume SN-194)
- Subscribers/subscription book, 1861-1864 (Offsite-box PE-80, Volume SN-195)
- Subscribers/subscription book, 1872-1881 (Offsite-box PE-80, Volume SN-196)
- Alphabetical list/register of members/subscribers, as of circa 1873 (Offsite-box PE-80, Volume SN-197)
- Alphabetical list/register of members/subscribers, as of circa 1881 (Offsite-box PE-80, Volume SN-198)
- Ledger of accounts (assets, revenue, expenditures), 1872-1873 (Offsite-box PE-81, Volume SN-199)
- Alphabetical list of visitors, 1864-1865 (Offsite-box PE-81, Volume SN-200)
- Record of memberships transferred to new members, 1889-1902 (Offsite-box PE-81, Volume SN-201)
- Annual dues, 1893-1901 (Offsite-box PE-81, Volume SN-202)
- Annual dues, 1872-1879 (Offsite-box PE-86, Volume SN-203)
- Annual dues, 1879-1886 (Offsite-box PE-86, Volume SN-204)
- Annual dues, 1886-1894 (Offsite-box PE-86, Volume SN-205)
- Annual dues, 1914-1922 (Offsite-box PE-86, Volume SN-206)
- Annual dues, 1900-1908 (Offsite-box PE-86, Volume SN-207)
- Annual dues, 1907-1914 (Offsite-box PE-88, Volume SN-208)
- Annual dues, 1930-1934 (Offsite-box PE-87, Volume SN-209)
- Annual dues, 1922-1930 (Offsite-box PE-87, Volume SN-210)
- Annual dues, 1938-1939 (Offsite-box PE-88, Volume SN-211)
- Annual dues, 1934-1938 (Offsite-box PE-88, Volume SN-212)
- Employee salary receipt acknowledgements. November 1950-February 1953, 1950-1953 (Offsite-box PE-87, Volume SN-213)
- Employee salary receipt acknowledgements. April 1945-November 1950, 1945-1950 (Offsite-box PE-87, Volume SN-214)
- Employee salary receipt acknowledgements. October 1939-April 1945, 1939-1945 (Offsite-box PE-88, Volume SN-215)
- Employee salary receipt acknowledgements. January 1934-November 1936, 1934-1936 (Offsite-box PE-89, Volume SN-216)
- Employee salary receipt acknowledgements. November 1936-September 1939, 1936-1939 (Offsite-box PE-89, Volume SN-217)
- Employee payroll ledger. May 1902-December 1928, 1902-1928 (Offsite-box PE-91, Volume SN-218)
  Data includes name, occupation, start/end date, and pay rate. Women employees identified with prefix "Miss."
- Employee payroll sheets, 1945-1952 (Offsite-box PE-90, Volume SN-219)
- Payroll (Buildings Department?), 1951-1955 (Offsite-box PE-138, Volume SN-220)
- Payroll (Buildings Department?), 1945-1950 (Offsite-box PE-139, Volume SN-221)
- Payroll (Buildings Department), 1938-1944 (Offsite-box PE-89, Volume SN-222)
- Securities ledger (investments), 1939-1947 (Offsite-box PE-140, Volume SN-223)
- Grain inspection. Suspense account. September 1914-December 1917, 1914-1917 (Offsite-box PE-92, Volume SN-224)
- Flour inspection department. Superintendent's accounts. March 1884-March 1917, 1884-1917 (Offsite-box PE-92, Volume SN-225)
- Flour inspection department. Inspection Fund journal. August 1931-September 1938, 1931-1938 (Offsite-box PE-92, Volume SN-226)
- Bills of lading, 1934-1938 (Offsite-box PE-93, Volume SN-227)
- Chemists Fund(?) General journal. October 1947-April 1951, 1947-1951 (Offsite-box PE-93, Volume SN-228)
- Cotton Seed Oil Chemists Fund. General journal. October 1908-April 1925, 1908-1925 (Offsite-box PE-93, Volume SN-229)
- Chemists Fund. General journal. November 1938-September 1947, 1938-1947 (Offsite-box PE-93, Volume SN-230)
- Chemists Fund. Daily cash receipts. June 1948-April 1951, 1948-1951 (Offsite-box PE-95, Volume SN-231)
- Chemists Fund. General journal? May 1925-December 1932, 1925-1932 (Offsite-box PE-93, Volume SN-232)
- Chemists Fund. General ledger, 1938-1950 (Offsite-box PE-95, Volume SN-233)
- Payroll records. Chemistry Department, 1937-1951 (Offsite-box PE-95, Volume SN-234)
- Expense journal. April 1920-October 1938, 1920-1938 (Offsite-box PE-103, Volume SN-235)
- Bank register ("Check book covering funds"). November 1947-April 1951, 1947-1951 (Offsite-box PE-104, Volume SN-236)
  Includes the General Fund, Flour Inspection Fund, Chemists Fund, and Grain Inspection Fund.
- Abstract of office and general expenses. April 1930-October 1938, 1930-1938 (Offsite-box PE-120, Volume SN-237)
- Record of payments and receipts. April 1931-October 1938, 1931-1938 (Offsite-box PE-121, Volume SN-238)
- Abstract of office and general expenses. May 1906-April 1920, 1906-1920 (Offsite-box PE-120, Volume SN-239)
- Securities ledger (investments), 1948-1949 (Offsite-box PE-120A, Volume SN-240)
- General ledger, 1930s-1940s (Offsite-box PE-141, Volume SN-241)
- Flour inspection fund. Journal and suspense accounts. April 1917-July 1931, 1917-1931 (Offsite-box PE-97, Volume SN-242)
- Journal entries. April 1942-December 1946, 1942-1946 (Offsite-box PE-98, Volume SN-243)
- Committee on Information & Statistics. Receipts & disbursements. 1921-May 1933, 1921-1933 (Offsite-box PE-97, Volume SN-244)
- Journal (General?). April 1919-April 1940, 1919-1940 (Offsite-box PE-96, Volume SN-245)
- Journal (General?). August 1904-March 1919, 1904-1919 (Offsite-box PE-96, Volume SN-246)
- Not used (Volume SN-247)
  There is no volume SN-247.
- General fund. Cash book (receipts & disbursements). November 1938-April 1946, 1938-1946 (Offsite-box PE-91, Volume SN-248)
- General fund. Daily cash receipts. May 1948-May 1951, 1948-1951 (Offsite-box PE-94, Volume SN-249)
- Ledger. July 1926-May 1932, 1926-1932 (Offsite-box PE-97, Volume SN-250)
- Ledger, 1905-1907 (Offsite-box PE-98, Volume SN-251)
- Grain inspection fund. Journal. May 1923-February 1937, 1923-1937 (Offsite-box PE-98, Volume SN-252)
- Ledger, 1893-1905 (Offsite-box PE-99, Volume SN-253)
- Ledger, 1907-1926 (Offsite-box PE-99, Volume SN-254)
- Ledger, 1886-1893 (Offsite-box PE-100, Volume SN-255)
- Ledger, 1878-1882 (Offsite-box PE-100, Volume SN-256)
- Ledger, 1892 (Offsite-box PE-100, Volume SN-257)
  Includes only a few entries. See also volume SN-274.
- Cash book/journal. January 1893-January 1897, 1893-1897 (Offsite-box PE-101, Volume SN-258)
- Cash receipts & disbursements. April 1905-April 1907, 1905-1907 (Offsite-box PE-105, Volume SN-259)
- Grain inspection fund. Cash book/journal. April 1930-October 1938, 1930-1938 (Offsite-box PE-102, Volume SN-260)
- Cash receipts & disbursements. May 1907-May 1911, 1907-1911 (Offsite-box PE-106, Volume SN-261)
- Cash receipts. May 1916-November 1918, 1916-1918 (Offsite-box PE-107, Volume SN-262)
- Cash receipts. December 1932-May 1937, 1932-1937 (Offsite-box PE-107, Volume SN-263)
- Cash receipts. June 1937-October 1938, 1937-1938 (Offsite-box PE-108, Volume SN-264)
- General fund. Voucher register. November 1938-October 1942, 1938-1942 (Offsite-box PE-108, Volume SN-265)
- Cash receipts. November 1938-October 1942, 1938-1942 (Offsite-box PE-119, Volume SN-266)
- Chemists Fund. General cash book. November 1938-April 1944, 1938-1944 (Offsite-box PE-118, Volume SN-267)
- Chemists Fund. Cash receipts & disbursements. May 1944-April 1951, 1944-1951 (Offsite-box PE-123, Volume SN-268)
- Cash receipts. November 1942-April 1946, 1942-1946 (Offsite-box PE-122, Volume SN-269)
- General Fund. Cash receipts. May 1946-April 1948, 1946-1948 (Offsite-box PE-118, Volume SN-270)
- Payroll records, 1947-1951 (Offsite-box PE-109, Volume SN-271)
- Subcommittee on Buildings. Minutes and reports, Book 1. July-December 1881 (Offsite-box PE-109, Volume SN-272)
  This primarily includes regular reports beginning with #1, likely related to the oversight of the construction of the new Exchange building at Bowling Green. The reports continue in volume SN-306.
- Special Committee on the New Exchange Building. Minutes. November 1881-November 1882, 1881-1882 (Offsite-box PE-109, Volume SN-273)
- Ledger, 1892 (Offsite-box PE-109, Volume SN-274)
  Includes only a few entries. See also volume SN-257.
- Special Committee on the New Exchange Building. March 1879-May 1879; Special notices, 1879-1882 (Offsite-box PE-109, Volume SN-275)
  The volume includes both the special committee minutes for March-May 1879 and a variety of special notices from 1880-82.
- Buildings Committee. Minutes. December 1883-May 1885, 1883-1885 (Offsite-box PE-109, Volume SN-276)
- Buildings Committee. Minutes. September 1892-October 1893, 1892-1893 (Offsite-box PE-109, Volume SN-277)
- Buildings Committee. Minutes. August 1879-October 1880, 1879-1880 (Offsite-box PE-110, Volume SN-278)
- Buildings Committee. Minutes. October 1880-October 1881, 1880-1881 (Offsite-box PE-110, Volume SN-279)
- Buildings Committee. Letterpress copybook. August-December 1879 (Offsite-box PE-110, Volume SN-280)
- Various special committees. Minutes. January 1912-August 1925, 1912-1925 (Offsite-box PE-110, Volume SN-281)
- Various special committees. Minutes. January 1904-February 1912, 1904-1912 (Offsite-box PE-110, Volume SN-282)
- Various special committees. Minutes. July 1893-December 1903, 1893-1903 (Offsite-box PE-111, Volume SN-283)
- Various special committees. Minutes. January 1878-June 1884, 1878-1884 (Offsite-box PE-111, Volume SN-284)
- Special Committee on Soybean Oil. Minutes. July 1944-November 1949, 1944-1949 (Offsite-box PE-111, Volume SN-285)
- Special Committee on Soybean Oil. Minutes. November 1938-March 1942, 1938-1942 (Offsite-box PE-111, Volume SN-286)
- Various committees. Minutes, 1930-1935 (Offsite-box PE-111, Volume SN-287)
  Includes minutes for at least four committees: Business Conduct, Arrangements, Securities, and Commissions.
- Business Conduct Committee. Minutes. March-December 1930 (Offsite-box PE-111, Volume SN-288)
- Business Conduct Committee. Minutes. March 1927-September 1950, 1927-1950 (Offsite-box PE-112, Volume SN-289)
- Committee on Custodian & Weighing. Minutes. May 1933-September 1937, 1933-1937 (Offsite-box PE-112, Volume SN-290)
  Also includes minutes of joint meetings with the Committee on Grain.
- Committee on Custodian & Weighing. Minutes. January 1935-December 1940, 1935-1940 (Offsite-box PE-112, Volume SN-291)
- Committee on Grain. Minutes. July 1930-December 1934, 1930-1934 (Offsite-box PE-112, Volume SN-292)
  Also includes minutes of joint meetings with the Committee on Custodian & Weighing.
- Committee on Grain and related special committees, 1940-1950 (Offsite-box PE-113, Volume SN-293)
- Committee on Information & Statistics. Minutes. January 1901-May 1910, 1901-1910 (Offsite-box PE-113, Volume SN-294)
- Committee on Information & Statistics. Minutes. June 1872-May 1883, 1872-1883 (Offsite-box PE-113, Volume SN-295)
- Committee on Information & Statistics. Minutes. July 1930-June 1935, 1930-1935 (Offsite-box PE-113, Volume SN-296)
- Committee on Information & Statistics. Minutes. January 1884-June 1988, 1884-1888 (Offsite-box PE-113, Volume SN-297)
- Committee on Information & Statistics. Minutes. June 1888-May 1893, 1888-1893 (Offsite-box PE-113, Volume SN-298)
- Committee on Provisions. Minutes. January 1873-July 1904, 1873-1904 (Offsite-box PE-114, Volume SN-299)
- Committee on Provisions. Minutes, 1901-1941 (Offsite-box PE-114, Volume SN-300)
  There is relatively little content in this volume, most of it from 1933.
- Special Committee on Popham Property, 1888-1892 (Offsite-box PE-114, Volume SN-301)
- Committee on Trade. Minutes. February 1872-May 1884, 1872-1884 (Offsite-box PE-114, Volume SN-302)
- Committee on Steamships. Minutes and correspondence, 1897-1952 (Offsite-box PE-102, Volume SN-303)
- Tallow Futures Committee. Minutes, 1935-1941 (Offsite-box PE-102, Volume SN-304)
  Includes minutes, correspondence, trade group registration and insurance records.
- Special Committee on Maritime Affairs. Minutes. January 1887-February 1892, 1887-1892 (Offsite-box PE-103, Volume SN-305)
- Reports to the Buildings Committee, Book #2. December 1881-March 1883, 1881-1883 (Offsite-box PE-103, Volume SN-306)
  These regular reports are likely related to the oversight of the construction of the new Exchange building at Bowling Green. See SN-272 for the earlier reports that precede these.
- Buildings Committee. Minutes. November 28, 1882-November 27, 1883, 1882-1883 (Offsite-box PE-103, Volume SN-307)
- Special Committee on Securities Trading. Minutes. November 2, 1927-October 31, 1928, 1927-1928 (Offsite-box PE-114, Volume SN-308)
- Committee on Hay & Straw. Minutes. August 9, 1893-July 24, 1930, 1893-1930 (Offsite-box PE-106, Volume SN-309)
- Index to unidentified record book, undated (Offsite-box PE-106, Volume SN-310)
  The index appears to relate to an accounting ledger.
- Index to unidentified record book, undated (Volume SN-311)
- Black pepper quotations (daily trades?). September 1941-April 1951, 1941-1951 (Offsite-box PE-115, Volume SN-312)
- Black pepper job lots. March 1950-January 1951, 1950-1951 (Offsite-box PE-116, Volume SN-313)
- Daily trades. Prime crude soybean oil. December 1950-June 1954, 1950-1954 (Offsite-box PE-117, Volume SN-314)
- Daily trades, 1900 (Offsite-box PE-128, Volume SN-315)
  Volumes SN-315 to SN-319 and SN-322 to SN-330 include records of daily trades for various goods. The volumes all appear to include wheat as their principal focus. Other goods seem to appear more unevenly over the time period (1900-1913), sometimes written on to pages that were pre-printed with labeling for other goods. Goods other than wheat that appear in at least some of these volumes include, possibly among others: corn, oats, white oats, cotton seed oil (CSO), pig iron, and lard.
- Daily trades, 1901 (Offsite-box PE-126, Volume SN-316)
- Daily trades, 1902 (Offsite-box PE-127, Volume SN-317)
- Daily trades, 1904 (Offsite-box PE-124, Volume SN-318)
- Daily trades, 1903 (Offsite-box PE-125, Volume SN-319)
- Committee on Grains, 1874-1875 (Offsite-box PE-115, Volume SN-320)
  Scrapbook-like compilation of printed rules on grading, published accounts of meetings, some news articles, etc.
- Quotations/prices. January 1916-October 1928, 1916-1928 (Offsite-box PE-120, Volume SN-321)
  Includes many types of goods, including: pork, beef, tallow, bellies, hams, dressed hogs, lard, petro, cotton oil, and others.
- Daily trades, 1905 (Offsite-box PE-137, Volume SN-322)
- Daily trades, 1906 (Offsite-box PE-136, Volume SN-323)
- Daily trades, 1907 (Offsite-box PE-135, Volume SN-324)
- Daily trades, 1908 (Offsite-box PE-134, Volume SN-325)
- Daily trades, 1909 (Offsite-box PE-133, Volume SN-326)
- Daily trades, 1910 (Offsite-box PE-132, Volume SN-327)
- Daily trades, 1911 (Offsite-box PE-131, Volume SN-328)
- Daily trades, 1912 (Offsite-box PE-130, Volume SN-329)
- Daily trades, 1913 (Offsite-box PE-129, Volume SN-300)
- Special Committee on Cotton Seed Oil Legislation (later, on CSO Rules or Contracts) (6 folders), 1924-1931 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1-6)
  Includes extensive correspondence, committee minutes, draft rules, and other documents related to the Produce Exchange's negotiations with U.S. Secretary of Commerce Herbert Hoover's Arbitration Committee to enact new rules for delivery on cotton seed oil contracts. Correspondence includes some letters to and from U.S. senators and congressmen as the matter related to federal legislation (S. 1414 of 1928).
- Board of Managers meeting documents (3 folders), 1934-1936 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 7-9)
  Includes agendas and related correspondence and other supporting documents for the meetings of December 20, 1934, August 1, 1935, and January 2, 1936.
- James Richardson & Sons Ltd. (Cross-libellant) vs. W.E. Hedger Transportation Corp (Cross-Respondent), 1937 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 10)
  This is Volume 3 of the proceedings (pages 1019-1077). For Volumes 1 and 2, see SN-80 to SN-89.
- Joint circular re: grading and delivery of grain in New York Harbor, 1875 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 11)
  Issued by the General Freight Agents of the Pennsylvania Railroad, New York Central & Hudson River Railroad, and Erie Railway, the circular communicates to their Western Agents and Connections the rules agreed with the Produce Exchange for the grading and delivery of grain.
- Bonded Grain Futures Market documents, 1926-1937 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 12)